automationanywhere.com 2019-10-26

# Privacy Policy and Your Choices Regarding Personal Information

Last Modified: September 24, 2019

The following describes the Automation Anywhere, Inc. ("Automation Anywhere," the "Company", “we,” “us,” or “our”) privacy policy and the manner in which Automation Anywhere collects, uses, shares and secures the personal information that it collects or receives via its website [www.automationanywhere.com](https://www.automationanywhere.com/), any sub-domain, other Automation Anywhere website and mobile applications (collectively, the “Sites”). It also describes your choices regarding use, access and correction of your personal information.

For purposes of the European Union General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), Automation Anywhere is both a data controller and processor of personal information collected by it via the Site.

What is Personal Information?

As used in this policy, "personal information" means any information that may be used, either alone or in combination with other information, to identify an individual. When we combine any non-personal information with personal information (e.g., technical information, such as the type of browser or operating system that you use), we treat the combined information as personal information.

Collection of Personal Information

  1. Personal information You Provide To Us 

Automation Anywhere may collect certain personal information when someone voluntarily sends a direct mail inquiry, an email or online registration, registers to download documents from the Sites, participates in seminars or webinars, requests Company information at tradeshows, applies for a job via the Sites, requests information, or purchases goods or services, via the Sites (including via our bot store located at [https://botstore.automationanywhere.com](https://botstore.automationanywhere.com/)).

Examples of such personal information include, but are not limited to, individual names, telephone numbers, email addresses, company name, mailing address, account user name and password, job title and financial information such as a credit or debit card number. If you apply for a job via the Sites, we may also collect personal information via your resume or any cover letter you choose to upload, or via any social media profile to which you elect to provide access.

We process personal information you provide to us either in connection with our legitimate business interests, or to the extent necessary for performance of a contract with you, your company, or our customer.

  2. Personal information Collected Through Cookies and Similar Technologies 

Automation Anywhere may collect certain information, including personal information, automatically from visitors to its Sites, and those of its subsidiaries, including the IP address, time visited, pages viewed and related information. When you visit the Sites, open emails from Automation Anywhere, use its apps or interact with its related tools, widgets or plug-ins, Automation Anywhere may collect certain information by automated means, such as through cookies, web beacons, local storage, scripts, pixels and web server logs. The information collected in this manner may include your IP address, unique device identifier, browser characteristics, domain and other system settings, search queries, device characteristics, operating system type, language preferences, referring URLs, actions taken on the Sites, dates and times of Site visits, metadata and other information associated with other files stored on your device.

Automation Anywhere uses Google Analytics to help analyze the traffic on the Sites. For more information on Google Analytics’ processing of personal information, please see https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/. You can opt out of Google Analytics by using the following Google provided browser plugin <https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/plugin/>.

We process personal information collected through cookies or similar technologies either in connection with our legitimate business interests in operating the Sites, performing the services, or operating our business, or otherwise to the extent you have agreed that we may do so.

  3. Mobile Applications 

When you download and use our mobile applications, we may automatically collect information on the type of device you use, operating system and version and system and performance information. We collect this information to help us measure app usage and better understand user demographics and event attendance. With your consent, we may send you push notifications from time-to-time in order to update you about any events or promotions that we may be running. If you no longer wish to receive these types of communications, you may turn them off at the device level.

We process personal information collected via our mobile applications in connection with our legitimate business interests in operating the Sites, performing the services, or operating our business, or otherwise to the extent you have agreed that we may do so.

  4. Personal information Collected Through Use of Our Services

Automation Anywhere may collect certain personal information that is provided in the course of the use of our services. This includes personal information contained in semi-structured and unstructured data hidden in electronic documents, images and emails provided by our customers when using our services. This data will be processed for the purposes of operating our Sites and providing our services. We also use this data for our internal training and quality purposes, and to enhance, research and analyze our service offerings and models. Examples of such personal information include, but are not limited to, individual names, telephone numbers, email addresses, job titles and contact information contained in invoices or emails. Personal information may relate to our customer’s employees, contractors or their customers or service providers.

The legal basis for processing this personal information is (i) our legitimate interests namely performing our services, or monitoring and improving our Sites and services, or (ii) necessity for performance of a contract between you, your company or our customer, and us.

Uses of Personal Information

Automation Anywhere uses your personal information to monitor the performance, and improve the quality of, its Sites, respond to requests about the Company and its business, provide information about products and services fulfill customer requests and for other business purposes and/or to comply with various legal and regulatory obligations. With your consent, Automation Anywhere may also use your personal information to send you information about its other products and services and for other specified marketing purposes. Unless we obtain your consent to processing of your personal information, Automation Anywhere processes your personal information either for performance of a contract with you or in circumstances where it has a legitimate interest to do so.

Automation Anywhere may use information collected through cookies, web beacons, pixels, web server logs and other automated means for purposes such as (a) customizing user visits to the Sites, (b) delivering content tailored to users' interests and the manner in which our users browse the Sites, and (c) managing the Sites and other aspects of its business.

You can change your cookies settings in your browser, however please note that without cookies you may not be able to use all of the features of the Sites. For more information about the cookies we use on the Sites, please click [here](https://www.automationanywhere.com/cookies).

Sharing of Personal Information

Automation Anywhere may share your personal information with its affiliates and subsidiaries, and/or with its business partners, in order to respond to customer needs or otherwise provide services to customers as requested. Automation Anywhere may also, with your consent, engage in joint marketing activities with such third parties and/or disclose personal information to third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. Whereas our data practices and your choice options are described in this Privacy Policy, we encourage you to consult the third party’s privacy policy to ensure that you understand how it intends to use your information and how you may exercise control over it.

Automation Anywhere may also share your information with its third-party agents who may be acting on its behalf and pursuant to its instructions to assist in our business activities, including, for example, providing notice of an upcoming webinar or tradeshow that may be of interest to the target audience, providing customer service, payment processing or providing storage services.

Automation Anywhere may disclose your personal information if it is required to do so by law or court order, to enforce or apply its Terms or if it believes in good faith that such release is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of its company, customers, affiliates or others.

Automation Anywhere also may share or transfer information, including your personal information, in connection with the sale, transfer, acquisition, merger, acquisition, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, bankruptcy or other change or ownership or control by Automation Anywhere or any affiliated company (in each case, whether in whole or in part). When one of these events occurs, Automation Anywhere will use reasonable efforts to notify users before their personal information is transferred or becomes subject to different privacy practices.

Automation Anywhere sometimes partners with other companies in order to provide their services via a link on the Site, for example job applications, social media links and live chat. In those circumstances, the third party partners will have access to the personal information you provide to them via their website, and we do not have any control over how they use that personal information. In order to fully understand how your personal information is used by our partners, please carefully review their applicable privacy policies. Except as set forth herein, Automation Anywhere does not share your personal information with any third parties.

Other Uses of Personal Information

In addition to the uses described above, Automation Anywhere will inform individuals of any other intended uses of their personal information at the time such personal information is collected or before such use is implemented including disclosure to third parties.

Data Security and Retention

Automation Anywhere uses reasonable methods to secure all personal information by a variety of methods, including restricting access to such personal information only to those people who have a legitimate need to know in order to discharge their job responsibilities on behalf of Automation Anywhere, securing access to the facility where the personal information is stored and the use of technology and physical controls to secure the personal information. Automation Anywhere is required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. If you have questions about the security of your personal information, please contact us as described below.

We may retain your personal information for as long as it is needed to fulfill the purposes described in this privacy policy, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes or enforce our agreements. Or, we will retain such personal information for so long as we have a lawful basis to process it, as set forth in this policy and with respect to (1) personal information processed by us in connection with our provision of support services, within 90 days after the associated help desk ticket is closed, and (2) all other personal information collected through use of our services, within (30) days after the termination of the applicable contract between you, your company or our customer and us.

Security of Personal Information by Third Parties

Automation Anywhere will require that all third parties acting on behalf of Automation Anywhere, and to which personal information is provided, give Automation Anywhere adequate contractual assurances that they will safeguard all such personal information in a manner consistent with this policy.

Children under the Age of 16

The Sites are not intended for children under the age of 16. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect personal information from anyone we know to be under 16 years of age.

Advertising and Newsletters

We may from time to time allow certain third parties to display advertising on our Sites or to manage our advertising on other sites. These third-party partners may use cookies or similar technologies such as web beacons, script, and pixels in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you would prefer to not receive personalized ads based on your browser or device usage, you may generally express your opt-out preference to no longer receive tailored advertisements. Please note that you will continue to see advertisements, but they will no longer be tailored to your interests.

To opt-out of interest-based advertising by participating companies in the following consumer choice mechanisms, please visit:

  * Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA)’s self-regulatory opt-out page (http://optout.aboutads.info/) and mobile application-based "AppChoices" download page (https://youradchoices.com/appchoices)
  * European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance (EDAA)'s consumer opt-out page (http://youronlinechoices.eu)
  * Network Advertising Initiative (NAI)’s self-regulatory opt-out page (http://optout.networkadvertising.org/).

In the mobile environment, most mobile operating systems offer device-based opt-out choices that are transmitted to companies providing interest-based advertising. To set an opt-out preference for a mobile device identifier (such as Apple's IDFA or Android's GAID), visit the device manufacturer's current choice instructions pages, or read more about sending signals to limit ad tracking for your operating system here: http://www.networkadvertising.org/mobile-choices.

Please note that these settings must be performed on each device (including each web browser on each device) for which you wish to opt-out, and if you clear your cookies or if you use a different browser or device, you will need to renew your opt-out preferences.

We will use your personal information to send you email or newsletters, if you have signed-up to receive them. If you would like to discontinue receiving this information, you may update your email preferences by using the “unsubscribe” link found in emails we send to you, or at your member profile on our website, or by contacting us as described below. You may not opt-out of service-related communications, which are not promotional in nature. Please note that even if you opt out of receiving the foregoing emails, we may still send you a response to any "Contact Us" request as well as administrative, maintenance and operational emails (for example, in connection with a password reset request).

ACCESS TO YOUR PERONAL INFORMATION

Upon an individual’s request, Automation Anywhere will provide reasonable access to any personal information it has about that person. Automation Anywhere will also take reasonable steps to allow such individuals to correct, change, modify or delete any such personal information that is shown to be incorrect, inaccurate or incomplete. You may ask us to delete the personal information we hold about you, or cease processing such personal information, in certain circumstances. It may not be possible for us to delete or cease processing all of the personal information we hold about you where we have an ongoing relationship with you or where we have a legal basis to retain such personal information.

You may access, correct, or request deletion of your personal information by logging into your account or by contacting us at [https://www.automationanywhere.com/data-subject-access-rights-request-form](https://www.automationanywhere.com/data-subject-access-rights-request-form/). We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

When we process personal information on the basis that you have consented to such processing, you have the right to withdraw your consent, or ask us to stop or restrict processing the personal information we have about you, at any time by contacting us using the contact information below.

You may also ask us to transfer your personal information to a third party in certain circumstances. If you would like any further information about your rights or how to exercise them, please contact us using the contact information below.

If you are in the European Union, you have the right to make a complaint at any time to the relevant data protection authority in your country. We encourage you to first reach out to us at [privacy@automationanywhere.com](mailto:privacy@automationanywhere.com).

Territories

Personal information collected by Automation Anywhere may be stored and processed in your geographic region, in the United States or in other countries in which Automation Anywhere, or its service providers, maintain facilities or operations. If you are in the European Economic Area, it may be necessary for your personal information to be transferred to, and processed in, other countries including the United States. If we transfer your personal information outside of the European Economic Area we use a variety of legal mechanisms, which may include contractual terms, to protect your rights with respect to your personal information.

Tracking

We do not track users over time and across third party websites to provide targeted advertising. Accordingly, we do not currently respond or take any action with respect to web browser "do not track" signals or other mechanisms that provide consumers the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of personal information about an individual consumer's online activities over time and across third-party web sites or online services.

However, some of our service providers and advertisers may use cookies or other methods to gather information regarding your use of the Sites and may combine the information in these cookies with any personal information about you that they may have. The use of such tracking information by a third party is subject to its privacy policy.

Your California Privacy Rights

If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information (as defined by California law) by Automation Anywhere to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [privacy@automationanywhere.com](mailto:privacy@automationanywhere.com) or write to us using the contact details below.

EU – U.S. Privacy Shield and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks

Automation Anywhere participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework (each, a “Framework” and collectively, the “Frameworks”). We are committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries and Switzerland, in reliance on each Framework, to such Framework’s applicable Principles. To learn more about the Frameworks, and to view our certification, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield List at https://www.privacyshield.gov.

Automation Anywhere is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under each Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Automation Anywhere complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU and Switzerland including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Frameworks, Automation Anywhere is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission.

In certain situations, Automation Anywhere may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website at https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint, you may be entitled to invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

Changes

Automation Anywhere may amend or modify this policy from time to time. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by posting the amended or modified version on its website at [https://www.automationanywhere.com](https://www.automationanywhere.com/). This policy may also be changed, or limited, to comply with legal or regulatory requirements, or as otherwise allowed or required by law.

Contact Information

Questions or comments about this policy, or concerns or complaints about possible violations, should be sent to [privacy@automationanywhere.com](mailto:privacy@automationanywhere.com) or to:  
Automation Anywhere, Inc.  
Attn: Legal Department  
633 River Oaks Parkway  
San Jose, CA 95164  
United States of America

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third-party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at [https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request.](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request)

Our European representative, as required by the European Union General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), can be contacted at: [privacy@automationanywhere.com](mailto:privacy@automationanywhere.com) or to:  
Legal Department, Data Privacy Officer  
Automation Anywhere UK Limited  
Level 35, Tower 42, 25 Old Broad Street  
London, EC2N 1HN  
England  
+44 (20) 37908260 or  
+44 (20) 37908834

#### Go Be GreatTM.

Automation Anywhere empowers people whose ideas, thought and focus make the companies they work for great. We deliver the world’s most sophisticated Digital Workforce Platform making work more human by automating business processes and liberating people.

##### Products

Our platform is powerful enough to automate tasks of any complexity, but user-friendly enough for anyone on your team to use.

##### Services

The Automation Anywhere services team has worked with companies of all sizes to automate their business processes for them, help discover new automation ideas, and maximize ROI.
